(IN BROOKLYN ACCENT)
Hey, everybody!
It's closing time!
You don't gotta go home,
but you can't stay here.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHOOPS)
Closing time!
Every office needs an
end-of-the-day tradition.
Something to tell you
the day's over.
Otherwise, you go home
and the night just
feels like more day.
It's weird.
Closing time!
W, R, K.
One last call
for alcohol so...
No, it's W, R, K,
as in kitten?
...so finish your
whiskey or beer!
Oh, my boss is
singing Closing Time,
maybe that's
what you're hearing.
ANDY: Come on, Pam!
BOTH: Closing time!
Time for you to go home
to the places you will be from
Let's see,
Andy has been manager
for 105 days,
which means I've heard
Closing Time 105 times.
Still don't know the words.
(SINGING INDISTINCTLY)
Home and home and home
I know who I want
to take me home!
to take me home
I know who I want
Take me home
You know what? Fine!
I try to start fun
traditions for you guys,
but if you don't want
to sing, no traditions!
Closing time!
Every new beginning...
I never heard that song
before and once I heard it,
I did not care for it.
But that song means
it's time to go home.
Now, it's my favorite song.
Every new beginning
comes from
some other beginning's end
Good night!
This report is atrocious.
Who's your favorite
Iron Chef?
You go first.
The ticketing software
paints a picture
of a sloppy, careless,
error-prone office.
Well, the monitoring software
is a double-edged sword.
Sometimes the...
Sorry. Go ahead.
Mmm-hmm.
Did you need
something from us?
Yes.
(SIGHS)
Your attention,
because...
No. That is all.
Last night,
I dreamed that
the number two
was the most valued
number in the world.
The Vice President
had all the power,
athletes fought
for silver medals,
women were considered
the best gender.
And stadiums of fans shouted,
"We're number two!"
As with all my dreams,
I'm guessing
it was about
my fear of immigrants.
Last week, an accounting
mistake resulted in
a client getting
their order for free.
Ohh! That's not good.
Chalk that one up
to "Tweedle-Dee"
and "Tweedle-Dum" out there.
Who are they?
They're both Kevin.
Oscar's the
Sex and the City gang,
and Angela, if you can...
Andy, sometimes
I feel like you don't
know me at all.
I would agree with that.
Simply end the mistakes.
End the mistakes. Easy.
When I come back next
week, and this report
shows me "No mistakes,"
we can talk
about names all day.
Our favorite names,
silly made-up names,
normal names said
in a silly voice.
Wouldn't that be nice?
I would like that.
End the mistakes.
That's all I ask.
And you can't have
a favorite Iron Chef.
It depends entirely on
the secret ingredient.
Sometimes I feel you
don't know food at all.
I'm just saying,
with the NBA lockout,
I think roller derby's
in a really good
place right now.
So, my pitch is, me, Pam,
you and someone else,
maybe Justine...
(GRUNTS)
No. Not Justine.
Never Justine.
Is that off again?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Hey, mandatory
warehouse safety
meeting today.
We don't really do those.
We just sign the thing.
Are you really this lazy?
I'll be there.
Hey.
Mondays suck!
Yeah. Yep.
Just trying to...
I may have a little solution
to our mistakes problem.
This is a project
I've been working on
for quite some time.
And today might be
the day to use it.
What've you got?
Allow me.
You're gonna love this.
(GRUNTS) Should've used
a shorter string.
Never mind,
I know it by heart.
It is a system that
holds people accountable
for everyone else's work.
Sounds controversial.
Have I not been
worthy of your trust?
a reliable number two?
Do not go there.
You're the deuce
I never want to drop.
Well, I can make this work.
I'll set it up right now.
I just need your go ahead.
Go do the voodoo
that you do so well!
I will do my voodoo.
Mmm-hmm.
Hey. I need you to get
the paperwork rolling
on a new
workplace relationship.
For you?
Yes, for Gabe.
Who are you seeing?
That's great.
Whom I am seeing is Val,
from down in the warehouse.
I'm not technically
seeing her,
but, I've seen
her with the eyes.
And there was attraction
in at least one direction,
so...
You know, I don't have
to do paperwork unless
you're actually dating.
Okay. Well, once this starts,
it's gonna be moving fast,
it's gonna be hot and heavy,
and I don't want
a bunch of
bureaucratic red tape
wrapped around my jock,
you know?
But I mean,
well, have you
talked to her?
Yeah. We had a whole
conversation about Mondays.
Do you know
her last name yet?
Toby, I'm gonna tell you
her last name tomorrow,
because she's gonna be
screaming it tonight.
She's gonna be screaming
her own last name?
Hey, watch it.
Good luck, Gabe.
Hi, guys.
Hi.
I just wanna say that
you all have been doing
amazing work, really.
Thank you.
And I'd like to add
that your work has
been a little sloppy.
So, Dwight and I
have implemented
a new program that
we like to call...
...Dwight?
The Accountability Booster.
It registers every time
a mistake has been
made in the office,
from a late delivery,
to an accounting error.
Five strikes in a day
equals a home run.
One home run
and you're out.
If we as a group make
five mistakes in a day,
something bad happens.
Like, we block Minesweeper!
Or, in this case,
an e-mail gets sent
to Robert California
containing the
consultant's report
from last year.
Remember the one
that recommended
the branch be shut down?
ALL: What?
And, as a failsafe, also,
every negative e-mail
you've ever written
about him to the group
will also be
forwarded to him.
What e-mails are
you talking about?
Robert's favorite
songs, Creep by TLC,
Creep by Radiohead.
You remember that one, Jim?
"There's no way
he hasn't strangled
at least one stripper."
Oscar.
"He eats his yogurt
like he is punishing it
for disappointing him."
Kelly.
That's not that
bad, actually.
PS, "We should
kill him."
Wait. So, you installed
a doomsday device?
No, it's an
Accountability Booster.
Which, when it goes off,
it destroys everything,
very similar to
a doomsday device.
Jim, you're trying
to make me sound like
some kind of evil maniac.
No, the point is,
is that we are now
working in an environment
where we have
accountability
to each other.
I am confident
that you guys are
equal to the task.
No, we're not.
And you are a psycho
who is ruining our lives.
We can't do this, Dwight.
We can't.
(ALL GRUMBLING)
Smile.
Nod. Smile and nod.
They're making me out
to be a Bond villain.
I like to think of myself
as a brilliant scientist
who will stop at nothing
to remake the world.
Like...
(SIGHS)
Not Doctor Moreau,
someone good.
Doctor Frankenstein.
Doctor Jekyll, not them.
Doctor...
Are you sure
this is a good idea?
I mean, the thing
about this office is,
we make a lot of mistakes.
But the device
will change that.
Without a safety net,
people will improve.
All right, everybody,
looks like we need to
be getting to work.
Be extra careful,
double-check everything.
Or the Accountability Booster
will get you.
This doomsday device
sounds like
a scare tactic to me.
There's an easy way to tell
if this device is a sham,
we just make a mistake.
I'll send an order
down to shipping before
we've received payment.
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
DWIGHT: (EXCLAIMS)
There's one mistake.
Now we only have
four strikes left
until a home run.
Dwight's our co-worker
and he worked really hard
on this doomsday
device. So, I...
It's not a doomsday
device! Gosh!
We can do this, you guys.
First!
Second!
It's not a race.
Third!
Who knows
what the belt is for?
GABE: It's for
protecting my ass
when you suckers
lift more than
you can handle.
What's up? I'm Gabe.
Corporate. Continue.
Don't be nervous.
Apparently,
we have a visitor.
Gabe, everyone.
Hi, Gabe!
All right,
so the support belt.
Now this one is mine.
Doesn't get much
use nowadays.
Look at this.
This is enormous.
I get the sense
that Val enjoys
a good put-down.
Considering
that's the only thing
I know about her,
I will be milking that hard.
It's like a hula-hoop,
right?
Mele Kalikimaka
is Hawaii's way
(WAREHOUSE WORKERS LAUGHING)
You done?
The Michelin Man called,
he wants his cummerbund back.
Remember, we have
to get Regal Escrow
their refund by 5:00.
I'm on it!
Kevin,
maybe I should
handle that.
We really need you to
focus on your project.
Good thinking.
Apparently,
a big client for
this company
needs to know the story
of how paper gets made.
Oscar, use a calculator.
When the stakes are this high
there's only one computer
that I trust.
And it's powered by
Thai food and Spanish reds.
All right, everybody,
you're doing great.
Well, I wouldn't say
that. Three mistakes
already is pretty terrible.
But I do see
improvement.
Meredith kept someone
on hold for 30 minutes,
and now look,
she's hard at work.
Dwight, question.
No questions.
If this doomsday
device goes off...
Accountability Booster.
If this bad idea goes off
and we all lose our
jobs, are you gonna
feel good about that?
I haven't even
considered it.
That's how sure I am
that this Accountability
Booster is gonna work.
Try "Mose-1-2-3-4."
Dwight would
never be that obvious.
Try something like...
"Z-6-4-$-8."
Not that exactly, Jim,
something like that.
Okay.
How about
"Scranton-Strangler-6-6-6"?
Nope.
No?
Aw...
Shoot. (LAUGHING)
You guys are never gonna
shut down the machine, okay?
But I appreciate your energy
and your teamwork.
You apply this to
your regular work,
you won't even notice
that the device is there,
watching you,
ready to strike.
What's Dwight's
mother's name?
Hedda.
No.
Once you've read
the packet, sign the back.
Hey, Darryl.
I was thinking,
maybe while we
read through this,
you could grab us
all some coffee?
My treat.
Here's a $100 bill.
That should cover it,
I think.
Don't bring me any
of that caramel soy
latte crap, okay?
I want a decaf
frappuccino.
Val?
Actually, Val,
why don't you come with?
I'll need the extra hands
to carry them back.
VAL: Yeah, sure.
Mmm-hmm.
Caramel soy latte.
No, a decaf frap.
Got it.
You sent the late
notice to Rinehart
and Wolfe, right?
Mmm-hmm. 64620.
67620.
Nuh-uh.
Yes!
588 plus 15%...
Oh, no!
KEVIN: What does this mean?
What does it mean?
OSCAR: Andy.
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
Oh!
(GASPS)
God!
That's five strikes.
Well,
I was saving this
for my retirement
which I guess is today.
Dwight, we got
five strikes.
Really?
Did the e-mail
go out or...
It goes out
automatically
at 5:00 p.m.
Well, then there's
gotta be a way to stop it.
Well, I would have
to enter my password
in order to cancel it.
Okay!
Dwight, you may now
enter your password.
No.
ANDY: What?
What?
You don't deserve
to have this branch.
Five mistakes in
less than a day?
We did our best.
No, you didn't, Phyllis.
You complained
the whole time,
you yelled at me,
you tried to break
into the machine.
(ALL PROTESTING)
DWIGHT: What?
You're a real crumb bum,
you know that?
Hey, you can't
just change the rules
because you don't
like the outcome.
What about you, Kevin?
What about you
and your fake task?
Can you tell me now
where paper comes from?
The man tree
puts its penis...
Okay. All right, Andy,
back me up here, please.
No.
What?
No!
Dwight, be human for once,
shut down the machine.
Shut it down!
Shut it down.
Shut down the machine!
Shut it down!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Good luck finding
a new job, idiots.
I'll make sure to write
you a glowing reference.
Glowingly negative!
Dwight's car is gone.
I bet he went home.
Some of us should go
there, try to talk
some sense into him.
Get him to stop that e-mail.
Pam, you should come with
me. Dwight really likes you,
and your breasts are
enormous, that could help us.
Kevin has that lovability.
Guys, come on!
I'm right here.
Jim, I want you
to go find Robert.
Just be where he is,
in case that e-mail
goes out at 5:00,
you can try to
delete it or something.
Okay. Where is he?
He's at some club
where you either eat
squash or play squash.
I'll try both.
Oh.
Did you come to
reason with me?
Got you something.
And I just really
want to talk to you.
Get lost.
Well, now hold on...
What are you doing?
What does it
look like I'm doing?
Digging a grave
for a horse.
Do you need a hand?
Yeah, you need a hand?
If you hit another horse,
you've dug too far.
ROBERT: I'll see you
next week, Will.
Robert!
Jim, what are you...
What a surprise!
Yeah. Well, you know,
I just had a meeting,
a squash meeting.
Yeah?
You up for a game?
A game? Or a match?
(CHUCKLES)
Exactly! Here we go.
Let's do it.
Are you okay, Kevin?
Where are you going?
In. I'm hungry.
Could we come in, too?
Just for some water?
Okay. Take off your shoes.
Except you, Kevin.
They stay on.
Wow, I forgot how
pretty your house is.
This is the newest
addition, built by
Erasmus Schrute in 1808.
It doubled as
a tuberculosis recovery
room until 2009.
That's too much doodle,
and not enough lab.
Yeah, when are
they gonna do a Labradoodle
that's just lab?
That's what I'm saying.
Hey.
You're welcome.
Thanks for the coffee.
So, tonight I was thinking,
I'm gonna go to the cemetery,
I'm gonna drink
a little wine,
and I thought
maybe you'd like
to come with me.
Are you asking me
on a date?
Yes, I am.
Because I don't
date coworkers.
It's not personal.
It's a matter of policy.
I could quit.
Problem solved.
Don't quit.
Good policy.
It's sensible.
Smart.
All right. Serving.
Serving, serving, serving.
In the box.
Why haven't
we heard anything?
It's 4:45.
There's only
15 minutes left.
Oh, now you
can do math?
Where were you
two hours ago,
beautiful mind?
I made a mistake,
I'm sorry!
I know how to save
the company, everyone.
Just write a petition,
get everyone's signature,
including our clients,
march down to Florida
and shove it up your butt.
(STANLEY LAUGHING)
It's not that funny.
Pam, you got
something on
your shirt.
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Well, pobody's
nerfect, right?
Did you just
have a stroke, Pam?
It's "nobody's perfect."
Nice stroke, Pam.
No, it's a jokey saying.
"Pobody's nerfect."
Like, I can't even
say those words right.
I hadn't heard that before.
That's funny.
Dwight,
there's just
the small...
You know what
would go so great
with this cabbage pie?
Milk.
Any specific animal?
I'm thinking cow.
Don't say cow.
What are you doing?
It's five to 5:00.
Just don't talk
about the e-mail, okay?
He's gonna
cancel it on his own.
I really think he will.
That's insane!
Just trust me.
Trust you?
Like I trusted
Dwight this morning?
I got this.
(GRUMBLING)
(SIGHS)
Thanks for everything.
Sive drafely.
Wasn't it supposed
to be drive safely?
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
Is that my phone?
Sounded like mine.
No, I think it's mine.
Let me just check
real quick here.
All right.
No, it's mine.
You took it out of my bag.
Oh. Oops.
Yeah.
Can I have it?
Yes.
Right now?
There you go.
Whoa! No! Wait, wait!
What the (BLEEP)?
JIM: Oh, man.
I'm sorry!
Jesus!
Did it break?
No, it's good, thanks.
You sure?
Yeah.
What kind of
iPhone is that?
It's the standard one,
the one everyone has.
Yeah. I have
the one that
nobody has.
Is there anything
interesting?
It depends, Jim.
Do you find one-day-only
JetBlue sales to
Buffalo interesting?
No, I don't.
All right!
Well, I am sore and
obviously horrible at this.
My serve!
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
Dwight stopped the device!
ALL: Yes!
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
He stopped it!
ALL: Yes!
We still have our jobs.
They're not
my favorite people
in the world.
I wouldn't even
call them friends.
They come over here,
eat my pie,
dig the crappiest horse grave
you've ever seen.
God, I'm gonna have
to work with them
forever, aren't I?
Just take it easy.
Nice and easy.
(GROANS)
Classic, right?
ROBERT: Ooh!
I'm all right.
You all right?
Yeah.
Skinned knee.
(GROANS)
Need a little ice
on that, maybe.
Yeah. That does
not feel good.
Okay. My serve.